This website uses cookies. By continuing to use this website you are giving consent to cookies being used. For more information on cookies and how you can disable them visit [Use of Cookie Policy](https://www.sanyo-av.com/us/support/cookie.php).

##### [](http://www.sanyo-av.com/us/index.php)

Privacy Policy /  
Terms and Conditions
=======================================

#### Privacy Policy

Funai Corporation, Inc., the seller of the products described on this website, respects the privacy of our customers and users of this site. This Privacy Policy identifies the practices of Funai Corporation, Inc. and its affiliates in the United States (collectively, “Funai”) as they relate to the collection, maintenance, use and sharing of personal information (which is information that identifies you or is about you) collected through this web site.  
  
**Data Privacy at Funai**  
Funai has established a comprehensive privacy program, including a global privacy office and a chief privacy officer, designed to help us respect and protect your data privacy rights. This statement includes both Funai’s commitment to and compliance with all applicable U.S. laws and regulations and this Privacy Policy.  
  
**Information about Purchasers of Our Products from Retailers**  
Funai collects the name and shipping address of purchasers of its products from retailers when Funai processes shipments of its products directly to such purchasers. Funai keeps in such cases in paper form a copy of the bill of lading, proof of delivery and internal invoices for approximately five (5) years to comply with any state audit of Funai for sales tax compliance and any other federal or state tax issues, at which time such documents are destroyed. If the order in question is made through a retail company’s web site, then in such cases Funai keeps in its computer files sales orders information and internal invoice information containing the customer’s name and address.  
  
In whatever form it may be, the Funai information as to a customer’s name and address is not sold to or shared with any third party.  
  
Should you wish to access any personal information held by Funai, you may do so by contacting Funai by email at [legaldept@funaicorp.com](mailto:legaldept@funaicorp.com) or by mail at Funai Corporation, Inc., 12489 Lakeland Rd., Santa Fe Springs, CA 90670, U.S.A. As noted above, when Funai ships its products to a consumer purchaser Funai keeps information in paper form as to the name and shipping address of such purchaser for approximately five (5) years to comply with state sales tax audit and federal and state tax compliance issues. After such time period is elapsed, the paper documents containing such information are shredded and destroyed. If similar information is kept by Funai in its computer system, you may request it be deleted once such time period has expired.  
  
Please be advised, that we reserve the right to disclose any personal information about you without your prior consent if we have a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to: (1) conform to legal requirements or comply with valid legal process, such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order; (2) protect our rights or property; (3) enforce the provisions of the Terms and Conditions; or (4) prevent harm to you or others.  
  
**Funai Website Privacy Statement**  
Funai respects the privacy of visitors to its websites; as a result, we have developed this website privacy policy. This website privacy policy applies only to the operation of websites that directly link to this policy when you click on “privacy statement” in the website footer. Through this website Funai does not collect information that can identify you, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, and other similar information.  
  
**Information that we Collect Automatically**  
We do collect certain types of information (“Other Information”) automatically whenever you access and use our websites. Other Information we collect may include your IP Address, the browser software you are using, your computer operating system, the date and time you access the website in question, and the internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our website, such Other Information that is so collected automatically does not include your name, address, telephone, e-mail address and other similar information, and other information gathered through our weblogs and cookies (see below) and information collected by Google Analytics and Search Console.  
  
This site may use a technology known as **web beacons** – sometimes called single-pixel gifs – that allow this site to collect **web log** information. A web beacon is a graphic on a web page or in an e-mail message designed to track pages viewed or messages opened. Web log information is gathered when you visit one of our websites by the computer that hosts our website (called a “webserver”). The webserver automatically recognizes some non-personal information, such as the date and time you visited our site, the pages you visited, the website you came from, the type of browser you are using (e.g., Windows 2000), and the domain name and address of your Internet service provider (e.g., AOL). We may also include web beacons in promotional e-mail messages in order to determine whether messages have been opened.  
  
This website may use a technology called a “**cookie**.” A cookie is a piece of information that our webserver sends to your computer (actually to your browser file) when you access a website. Then when you come back our site will detect whether you have one of our cookies on your computer. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the site and help us analyze site usage more accurately. For instance, our site may set a cookie on your browser that keeps you from needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the site.  
  
This website uses Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet. Generally, an IP address changes each time you connect to the Internet (it is a “dynamic” address). Note, however, that if you have a broadband connection, depending on your individual circumstance, it is possible that your IP Address that we collect, or even perhaps a cookie we use, may contain information that could be deemed identifiable.  
This is because with some broadband connections your IP Address doesn’t change (it is “static”) and could be associated with your personal computer. We use your IP address to report aggregate information on use and to help improve the website.  
  
You should be aware that this site is not intended for, or designed to attract, individuals under the age of 18. We do not collect personally identifiable information from any person we actually know is an individual under the age of 18.  
  
Areas of this website that collect Your Information use industry standard secure socket layer encryption (SSL); however, to take advantage of this your browser must support encryption protection (found in Internet Explorer release 3.0 and above).  
  
**How to Contact Funai**  
To contact Funai for information regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact the Web Coordinator by mail at Funai Corporation, Inc., 12489 Lakeland Rd., Santa Fe Springs, CA 90670, U.S.A., Attention: Web Coordinator, or by email at [legaldept@funaicorp.com](mailto:legaldept@funaicorp.com).  
  
**Effect of Visiting Our Websites**  
By visiting our websites, you agree to be bound by the terms outlined in this Privacy Policy.  
  
**Data Security**  
While we try to protect the integrity and security of our network and systems, we cannot and do not guarantee that our security measures will prevent unauthorized third-parties (often called “hackers”) from obtaining the information we have that is discussed herein without permission. We will use reasonable efforts to protect this information on our internal systems, but hackers or other unauthorized persons may obtain access to this information without our permission.  
  
**Cautions and Warnings**  
Please exercise caution when visiting our websites. It is your responsibility to maintain the security of your passwords and other financial and personal information. Your usage of this site constitutes an acknowledgement and assumption of these risks.  
  
Funai will not ask you for any personal information in any emails. Funai may send you electronic mail messages in accordance with United States law, but you should not respond to any electronic mail messages asking for your personal information, especially if the messages ask for your passwords or credit/debit card information. These messages are often called “phishing,” and they are designed to steal personal information for identity theft and other bad purposes.  
  
**Violation of this Privacy Policy**  
If at any time you believe Funai has not adhered to the principles set forth in this Privacy Policy, please notify us and we will make all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly correct the problem. We can be contacted at [legaldept@funaicorp.com](mailto:legaldept@funaicorp.com).  
  
**Revisions to this Privacy Policy**  
Funai reserves the right to revise, amend, or modify this policy and our other policies and agreements at any time and in any manner, effective upon posting the revised version of this policy on this web site.  
  
**Prior Version of this Privacy Policy**  
This version of this Privacy Policy revised the previous Policy in many ways, including by adding Your California Privacy Rights, defined Funai to include its affiliates, and added that new versions of the Privacy Policy are effective upon posting.

#### Your California Privacy Rights

Your California Privacy Rights identifies the practices of Funai and its affiliates (collectively, “Funai”) as they relate to the use and sharing of personal information about California residents collected through this web site.  
  
Under the law of the State of California, California residents who provide personal information via a web site or other online service, such as this web site, may request and obtain from Funai once each calendar year information about the personal information Funai shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. As noted previously, Funai does not have any such information and in any event does not share any information with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses.  
  
Should you think that Funai does have such information, please contact the Web Coordinator by mail at Funai Corporation, Inc., 12489 Lakeland Rd., Santa Fe Springs, CA 90670, U.S.A., Attention: Web Coordinator, or by email at [legaldept@funaicorp.com](mailto:legaldept@funaicorp.com). Please note that we do not provide this information in response to telephone requests, and we generally do not provide this information to any California resident more than once per calendar year.

#### Terms and Conditions

This web site is published and maintained by Funai and its authorized representatives. Access to or use of this web site constitutes an acknowledgement of and agreement to the Terms and Conditions outlined here. Funai reserves the right to modify or amend these Terms and Conditions and any web site content or service at any time, without notice, and without liability.  
  
**Other Web Sites that are not Affiliated with Funai**  
Links may be provided to other web sites that are not affiliated with Funai and are subject to their own Terms and Conditions of Use. These links are provided as a convenience. Funai is not responsible for any other web sites or the conduct of such third parties. Funai does not endorse other web sites and is not accountable for the accuracy of their content or for your use of other web sites.  
  
**Disclaimer**  
All information and services provided on this web site are provided AS IS and AS AVAILABLE. Funai makes no guarantee or warranty as to any information on this web site, or contained herein, or to any products or services sold or provided via this web site. Your use of this web site is AT YOUR OWN RISK. Funai does not guarantee the safety or security of this web site, its servers, components, equipment, code, or software. Under no circumstances shall Funai be liable for any damages or other form of relief resulting from the reliance upon information provided at this web site or the use, misuse, or inability to use this web site, or the information contained herein. Any and all products sold through this web site are subject to the written warranties, if any, included with or provided with the product.  
  
**Property**  
All contents and components of this web site are the exclusive property of Funai. Images, logos, text and other content are protected by copyright and and/or trademarks and may not be used, modified, removed, or altered in any way.  
  
Malicious uses of this material or attempts to interfere with the web site’s operation are prohibited and may be punishable by law. Any material or information submitted by users of this web site to Funai are the sole property of Funai, and by submitting the materials or information you transfer to Funai ownership of and any claim to the materials or information. This web site and all content are Copyright © Funai Corporation, Inc., which reserves all of its rights.  
  
**Claims of Copyright Infringement**  
If you believe that your work has been copied on our web site, or any of our other systems or networks in a way that constitutes infringement under the Copyright Act, please provide the following information to Funai for receipt of notification of claimed infringement (to ensure that your notification complies with the requirement of the Digital Millennium Copyright Act, please see 17 U.S.C. § 512(c)(3)):

* An electronic or physical signature of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest;
* A description of the copyrighted work that you claim has been infringed;
* A description of where the material that you claim is infringing is located on the site;
* Your address, telephone number, and email address;
* A statement by you that you have a good faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law;
* A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notification is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf.

Please note that we may update this Web site Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do update it, for your convenience, we will make the updated policy available on this page.  
  
Last Updated: April 28, 2021

©2023 [FUNAI CORPORATION, INC.](https://www.funai.us/) All rights reserved.
